Wang Ning.
Adjust your pose a little.
Lift your head and look up slightly.
Okay. 3, 2, 1.
One more shot.
3, 2, 1. Okay.
Does the brand want Yin Zixi as the model?
I've received the proposal.
Yeah, okay. That's all.
I see you're busy every day.
How much of the target have you completed?
It's already done.
Impossible.
The company didn't even notify me.
Did you plant a spy?
Ah.
Don't just think about work all day.
I heard
Yin Zixi is very popular
over at the school.
Uncle He, are you worried we'll catch up with the quota?
I'm worried you'll act like a block of wood.
Don't regret it when Yin Zixi is pursued
by someone else.
Okay, let's continue.
Move back a bit first.
Move back a little more.
Ah.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
That's it for today's shooting.
Good job, everyone.
I just sprained my ankle.
I'll be fine after a short rest.
I can shoot as long as I stand still.
We are taking a break today.
I'll do it myself.
Sit still.
What's wrong?
Hello, Uncle He.
Your father just called.
The investigation is over.
He just came back.
Really?
It's quite urgent.
I need to go back first.
Got it, Uncle He.
Can I go back then?
The flight is at 11:00 tonight.
Come if you can make it.
Okay.
My dad is back.
That's great.
You've been living off-campus all along?
There's an apartment above the restaurant.
It's more convenient to live here.
No wonder you don't interact much with other classmates.
Let's go.
President, she's here.
You must be Wen.
What do you want?
Haven't I already written the self-criticism for cheating?
Ah, you misunderstood.
I asked you to come here
mainly because I want to cooperate with you.
Cooperate?
I don't want to join your student union.
I heard you don't get along well with Yin Zixi.
Let's cooperate.
I'll be back in a few days.
Okay.
Can you handle it alone?
I can.
I know all the equipment in the live broadcast room.
Hey.
Is your foot still injured?
I told you it's fine.
I'm already recovered.
Look.
Zixi,
I have something to tell you.
The car is here.
Xi A 6M223.
Wait for me.
Okay.
That's a wrap for today.
Great job, everyone.
Yue S Z545U.
Look, that's the woman.
Let's go.
Hurry up.
Go.
An, bad news.
Someone's trying to harm Yin Zixi.
Driver, turn around.
What's wrong?
Turn around. I need to go back.
Ah.
What do you want?
I've called the police.
Oh, really?
Don't be nervous.
We are not bad guys.
Internet celebrities like you are just selling yourselves.
Name your price.
Money is not a problem.
Don't come any closer.
If you come any closer, I'll scream.
Scream.
No one will hear you even if you scream your lungs out.
Why don't you play with us for a while?
We'll treat you well.
Just you wait.
How are you?
Are you okay?
Why are you here?
It's the completely wrong direction from the school.
Because I'm bad with directions.
So what?
Okay.
Liu Mingde
Casting Director: Xi Chongjing
Props Assistant: Li Kunxiao
Set Vehicle: Yi Mingle
Sound Recordist: Sun Pengfei
Yi Tong
Production Company: Dongguan Huoren Film & TV Production Co., Ltd.
International Commerce Centre